export const Round1 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    level: 100,
    type: 1,
    question:"Name the trial comparing oral semaglutide  to empagliflozin, where primary endpoint was change in HbA1c from baseline to week 26.",
    options: ["PIONEER 2","PIONEER 3","SUSTAIN 2","SUSTAIN 3"],
    correctAnswer: "PIONEER 2",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
    timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    level: 100,
    type: 1,
    question:"Name the trial  where semaglutide delays the progression of renal impairment and lowers the risk of renal and cardiovascular mortality in subjects with type 2 diabetes and chronic kidney disease. ",
    options: ["SUSTAIN 6","PIONEER 6","FLOW","SOUL"],
    correctAnswer: "FLOW",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
    timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    level: 100,
    type: 1,
    question:"Both PIONEER 6 and SUSTAIN 6 are ______ _______ for semaglutide molecule both oral and injectable.",
    options: ["Preapproval CVOT","Postapproval CVOT","Event and time driven"],
    correctAnswer: "Preapproval CVOT",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
    timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    level: 100,
    type: 3,
    question:"The main organ contributing to Rybelsus® weight loss is:",
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "Brain",
    image: "",  
    audio:"",
    timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    level: 100,
    type: 1,
    question:"SUSTAIN 10 trial was to compare the efficacy and safety of semaglutide 1 mg vs ________ in adults with T2D.",
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "Liraglutide 1.2 mg",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
    timer:60
  }, {
    id: 6,
    level: 100,
    type: 1,
    question:"A prospective, non-interventional study, investigating the use of once-daily oral semaglutide in type 2 diabetes patients who intend to fast during Ramadan in real-world setting. ",
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "O-Sema-FAST",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  }, {
    id: 7,
    level: 200,
    type: 1,
    question:"In FLOW trial OW semaglutide s.c. 1.0 mg demonstrated _____ first composite kidney event, and this was the primary kidney endpoint. ",
    options: ["24% RRR","26% RRR","36% RRR","18% RRR"],
    correctAnswer: "24% RRR",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    level: 200,
    type: 3,
    question:"The biggest challenge addressed by Rybelsus® is:",
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "Fear of injection, Preferance for oral",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  }, 
  {
    id: 9,
    level: 200,
    type: 1,
    question:"In SUSTAIN 6 the risk of nephropathy was _______ lower with semaglutide vs placebo.",
    options: ["36% significantly","36% non-significant","24% significantly","24% non-significant"],
    correctAnswer: "36% significantly",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  
  {
    id: 10,
    level: 200,
    type: 3,
    question:"If you skip a dose of Ozempic® more than ____ days, you need to skip the weekly dose and take the next dose on the scheduled day.",
    options: ["3","4","5","7"],
    correctAnswer: "5",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    level: 200,
    type: 1,
    question:"In PIONEER 3, oral semaglutide 14 mg showed significant HbA1c and weight reduction vs sitagliptin in week 26 by ______ and _________respectively.",
    options: ["(-1.3%, -3.1 kg)","(-1.2%, -3.5 kg)","(-1.4%, -3.6 kg)","(-1.5%, 3.8 kg)"],
    correctAnswer: "(-1.3%, -3.1 kg)",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    level: 200,
    type: 1,
    question:"OW semaglutide s.c. 1.0 mg demonstrated ________ risk reduction of MACE in FLOW trial.",
    options: ["Significant 18% RRR","Non-significant 16% RRR","Significant 26% RRR","NS 26% RRR"],
    correctAnswer: "Significant 18% RRR",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    level: 300,
    type: 1,
    question:"In SUSTAIN 4, OW semaglutide 0.5 mg showed significant HbA1c and weight reduction vs insulin glargine by ______ and _________ respectively.",
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "(-1.2%, -3.5 kg)",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    level: 300,
    type: 3,
    question:"In Rybelsus® CLM: Describe the patient profile of Sarah.  (Age, BMI, other co-morbidities, medication)",
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "Young age, Early diabetes journye, HTN and Dyslipidemia, BMI above 30",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    level: 300,
    type: 1,
    question:"Subjects in both semaglutide treatment arms experienced significantly more weight loss compared with placebo: Weight reduction of 3.7 kg and 4.5 kg with semaglutide 0.5 mg and 1.0 mg, respectively in:",
    options: ["PIONEER 1","SUSTAIN 9","SUSTAIN 5","SUSTAIN 1"],
    correctAnswer: "SUSTAIN 1",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    level: 300,
    type: 3,
    question:'In Rybelsus® CLM: What does the "Y" represent in Rybelsus® READY patients?',
    options: [],
    correctAnswer: "Yet to require a medication with CV risk reduction",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    level: 300,
    type: 3,
    question:"Percentage of patients in PIONEER REAL, who found Rybelsus® easy or very easy to use.",
    options: ["75%","80%","85%","95%"],
    correctAnswer: "85%",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    level: 300,
    type: 1,
    question:"First non-fatal stroke was one of the components of the primary endpoint in PIONEER 6 where HR was ______ for semaglutide vs placebo.",
    options: ["1.18","0.74","0.56","0.49"],
    correctAnswer: "0.74",
    image: "",
    audio:"",
     timer:60
  },
  // Add more questions here
];
